Sam B. Hall, Jr. Papers, Inclusive: 1943-2005, undated Bulk: 1976-1985
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Events, 1975-2005, undated; 5
  - General, 1975-2005, undated; 1
    - Mail Sent Down to the District for Signature, 1977 August 3-11 (Box 265, Folder 9)
    - Traylor Russell Bar-B-Q, White Oak Valley Ranch, Titus County, TX, 1977 August 12 (Box 265, Folder 10)
    - Vocational Agriculture Teachers Association of TX, Distinguished Legislation Award, 1977 July 5-September 14 (Box 265, Folder 11)
    - American Association of Retired Persons, Inc. Kilgore Community House, 1977 May 16-September 9 (Box 265, Folder 12)
    - Mt. Pleasant Chamber of Commerce, 1977 May 20-October 27 (Box 265, Folder 13)
    - Bonham, 1977 August 2-October 27 (Box 265, Folder 14)
    - Tour of R.C. and D facilities, 1977 August 2-September 14 (Box 265, Folder 15)
    - City of Blossom, 1977 March 4-September 30 (Box 265, Folder 16)
    - Texarkana District Office and Rotary Club, 1977 May 2-September 1 (Box 265, Folder 17)
    - Buck Florence Appreciation Dinner, 1977 August 2-18 (Box 265, Folder 18)
    - Marshall District Office, 1977 July 14-21 (Box 265, Folder 19)
    - Pittsburg Kiwanis Club, 1977 June 28-September 2 (Box 265, Folder 20)
    - Tyler Chapter of the Texas Association of Business, 1977 July 27-September 27 (Box 265, Folder 21)
    - Athens Rotary Club, 1977 April 30-September 30 (Box 265, Folder 22)
    - Overton Rotary Club, 1977 August 3-October 4 (Box 265, Folder 23)
    - Civil Defense Awards Banquet, 1977 July 18-September 2 (Box 265, Folder 24)
    - New Boston, 1977 June 10-September 7 (Box 265, Folder 25)
    - Scottish Rite Dallas bodies, Marshall High School, 1977 June 16-September 1 (Box 265, Folder 26)
    - Paris District Office Aid, Paris Kiwanis Clubs, 1977 June 17-October 20 (Box 265, Folder 27)
    - Good Morning America Program, 1977 February 8-1978 February 3 (Box 265, Folder 28)
    - Texarkana District Office, 1977 July 21-August 26 (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Henderson VFW, 1977 August 31 (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Sabine Valley Regional Mental Health, Mental Retardation Center, “Ware Home”, 1977 June 14-September 21 (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - San Augustine Lions Club, 1977 August 4-December 23 (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Texas Breakfast Club, 1977 July 25-September 20 (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Commissioning of the USS TX, 1977 July 26-September 13 (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - East Texas Council of Governments, 1976 August 19-1976 September 23 (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - Ark-Tex Council of Governments, Titus County Civic Center, 1977 April-November 8 (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - National Hunting and Fishing Day, Paris, 1976 August 24-September 27 (Box 266, Folder 9)
    - General Savings Association, Henderson, 1976 September 2-27 (Box 266, Folder 10)
    - Baylor Development Council, 1977 September 1-October 15 (Box 266, Folder 11)
    - Jim Wright Appreciation Dinner, Wright Congressional Club, Green Oaks Inn, Ft. Worth, 1977 July 28-October 26 (Box 266, Folder 12)
    - Baylor Homecoming, 1977 March 3-October 26 (Box 266, Folder 13)
    - Hopkins County Farm Bureau, 1977 September 13-ovember 8 (Box 266, Folder 14)
    - Hallsville High School, Dedication, 1977 September 1-November 14 (Box 266, Folder 15)
    - Paris District Office, 1977 October 25-November 2 (Box 266, Folder 16)
    - Paris Lion Club, 1977 August 16-November 2 (Box 266, Folder 17)
    - Northeast Texas Bar Association, 1977 June 2-November 28 (Box 266, Folder 18)
    - Medallion Kitchens of Texas, Inc., First National Bank of Jefferson, 1977 October 27-November 17 (Box 266, Folder 19)
    - Northeast Texas Association of Soil and Water Conservation Districts, Pittsburg, 1977 June 16-November 30 (Box 266, Folder 20)
    - Bowie County Farm Bureau, 1977 May 3-November 11 (Box 266, Folder 21)
    - Linden Municipal Hospital Dedication, 1977 July 13-November 11 (Box 266, Folder 22)
    - Hallsville High School Vocational Technical Building Groundbreaking, 1977 October 19-November 2 (Box 266, Folder 23)
    - East Texas Chapter of Credit Unions, Knights of Columbus Hall, Marshall, TX, 1977 September 9-November 17 (Box 266, Folder 24)
    - District V Texas Farm Bureau, 1977 June 28-November 17 (Box 266, Folder 25)
    - L.P. “Pete” Patterson Dinner, Texas Power and Light Company Clubhouse in Johnstown, 1977 October 17-December 8 (Box 266, Folder 26)
    - Berwind Railway Service Company, Business Dinner at Highland Lake Club, 1977 October 26-November 16 (Box 266, Folder 27)
    - Winnsboro Service Clubs (1 of 2), 1977 September 19-November 25 (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - Winnsboro Service Clubs (2 of 2), 1977 September 19-November 25 (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - Shelby County Mental Health & Mental Retardation, 1977 September 16-December 2 (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - Timpson High School, 1977 October 19-November 17 (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - Texarkana District Office, 1977 September 21-November 18 (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - Dr. Denzer Burke, 1977 March 25-November 25 (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - Texarkana, Girl Scouts, 1977 October 7-November 18 (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - Naples Lions Club, 1977 August 26-November 20 (Box 267, Folder 8)
    - Marshall National Bank, 1977 October 18-November 23 (Box 267, Folder 9)
    - Marshall Classroom Teachers Association, 1977 October 19-November 22 (Box 267, Folder 10)
    - Mt. Pleasant Senior Citizens’ Center, 1977 October 11-1978 January 23 (Box 267, Folder 11)
    - Mt. Pleasant Kiwanis Club, 1977 September 19-December 6 (Box 267, Folder 12)
    - Bonham Christmas Parade, 1977 April 1-December 7 (Box 267, Folder 13)
    - Progressive Citizens League & Bonham Ministerial Alliance at Bradford Chapel A.M.E. Church, 1977 November 18-December 26 (Box 267, Folder 14)
    - Hawkins Inert Gas Plant, Hawkins, TX, 1977 November 15-December 27 (Box 267, Folder 15)
    - Caddo Pharmaceutical Association Excelsior, Jefferson, TX, 1977 September 19-December 9 (Box 267, Folder 16)
    - Rusk, TX, 1977 September 30-December 19 (Box 267, Folder 17)
    - All-American Kiwanis Club of Marshall, 1977 December 1-14 (Box 267, Folder 18)
    - East Texas State University at Texarkana, December Commencement, 1977 November 2-December 29 (Box 267, Folder 19)
    - Marshall Industrial Park Dedication, 1977 December 19-1978 July 2 (Box 267, Folder 20)
    - Texarkana District Office, 1977 December 30-1978 January 20 (Box 267, Folder 21)
    - Luncheon Meeting in Texarkana, 1978 January 9-20 (Box 267, Folder 22)
    - Texas Power and Light Company (1 of 2), 1977 April 11 (Box 267, Folder 23)
    - Texas Power and Light Company (2 of 2), 1977 April 11 (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Welsh Power Plant, SWEPCO, 1977 July 29 (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Beef Import Meeting, 1978 January 23 (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Agricultural Meeting, 1978 March 25 (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Meeting in Mount Pleasant with Farmers, 1978 March 28 (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Marshall Rotary Club, 1977 December 12-1978 January 19 (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - Pilot Club of Henderson, 1977 August 26-1978 January 19 (Box 268, Folder 7)
    - Items Sent for Use in State Democratic Auctions, 1977 December 19-1978 January 6 (Box 268, Folder 8)
    - Morris County Museum and Historical Society, 1977 November 15-1978 January 25 (Box 268, Folder 9)
    - Meeting in Paris with Farmers, 1978 January 16-18 (Box 268, Folder 10)
    - Mayor’s Prayer Breakfast in Marshall, 1978 January 10-25 (Box 268, Folder 11)
    - Meeting in Washington with Farmers, 1977 December 7-1978 January 31 (Box 268, Folder 12)
    - International Paper Company Reception, 1977 November 11-1978 January 20 (Box 268, Folder 13)
    - Texas Association of School Boards, 1978 January 6-February 14 (Box 268, Folder 14)
    - Wholesale Beer Distributors of Texas, Breakfast, 1977 December 19-1978 February 16 (Box 268, Folder 15)
    - Texas Bankers Association, Reception & Dinner, 1978 January 9-16 (Box 268, Folder 16)
    - Texas Good Roads/Transportation Association, Breakfast, 1977 December 15-1978 March 7 (Box 268, Folder 17)
    - Judiciary Conference, Colonial Williamsburg, 1977 September 29-1978 February 10 (Box 268, Folder 18)
    - Texas Hospital Association, Reception, 1978 January 7-February 13 (Box 268, Folder 19)
    - Houston Sheet Metal Contractors Association, Reception, 1978 January 12-16 (Box 268, Folder 20)
    - DSG O’Neill Dinner Dance, 1978 January 19-February 7 (Box 268, Folder 21)
    - National Pro-family/Pro-life Coalition, Luncheon, 1978 February 3 (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Delta County Farm Bureau, 1977 December 9-1978 February 2 (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - Marion County Chamber of Commerce, Banquet, 1978 January 4-February 27 (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Red River Valley Association, 53rd Annual Convention, 1977 December 9-1978 March 9 (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - J. C. Penney Company, Inc., Reception, 1978 January 19-February 22 (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Panama Canal, 1978 February 18-March 21 (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - Meeting with Farmers in Cooper, 1977 May 13-1978 March 9 (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - West Texas Chamber of Commerce, Reception, 1978 January 12-April 3 (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - Veterans of Foreign War, Congressional Dinner, 1977 December 23-1978 March 7 (Box 269, Folder 9)
    - Democratic Congressional Dinner, 1978 February 6-March 15 (Box 269, Folder 10)
    - KFYN Radio Broadcast, 1978 February 8-March 21 (Box 269, Folder 11)
    - Mt. Vernon Chamber of Commerce, Banquet, 1978 February 14-March 30 (Box 269, Folder 12)
    - East Texas City Managers Association, Johnny Cace’s, 1978 March 16-April 5 (Box 269, Folder 13)
    - Paris District Office, 1978 March 5-April 11 (Box 269, Folder 14)
    - Rick Deese, 1978 March 14-29 (Box 269, Folder 15)
    - Hallsville Chamber of Commerce, Banquet, 1977 December 5-1978 April 7 (Box 269, Folder 16)
    - Mrs. Jerry Shelton, 1978 February 28-March 29 (Box 269, Folder 17)
    - Ark-O-Tex Chapter of the Association of the United States Army, 1978 March 20-April 15 (Box 269, Folder 18)
    - Sulphur River Chapter of the Texas Society of Professional Engineers, 1977 December 19-1978 April 11 (Box 269, Folder 19)
    - Texarkana Bi-city Municipal Library, 1978 February 21-March 31 (Box 269, Folder 20)
    - Texarkana Chamber of Commerce, Governmental Affairs Luncheon, 1978 February 7-March 31 (Box 269, Folder 21)
    - Texarkana District Office, 1978 February 15-April 4 (Box 269, Folder 22)
    - Carthage Rotary Club, 1978 January 18-April 10 (Box 269, Folder 23)
    - Frank Johnson Breakfast, 1978 April 1-5 (Box 269, Folder 24)
    - Marguerite Ratcliff Dinner, 1978 March 13-April 20 (Box 269, Folder 25)
    - Avinger CSA Banquet, 1977 November 7-1978 May 1 (Box 269, Folder 26)
    - Ore City High School, Library/Cafeteria Dedication, 1977 October 11-1978 April 27 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Henderson MH-MR Center Dedication, 1978 March 21-May 2 (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - 31st Annual Pilgrimage Parade, 1977 December 29-1978 May 27 (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Marshall District Office, 1978 June 27-July 11 (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Wayne Smith Meeting, 1978 July 27-August 25 (Box 270, Folder 5)
    - Texas State Society Board Meeting, 1979 June 28-September 6 (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - Pfizer, Inc., 1978 July 26-October 3 (Box 270, Folder 7)
    - Bottlers Luncheon, 1978 August 15-October 14 (Box 270, Folder 8)
    - Rusk, Texas, 1978 August 1-October 12 (Box 270, Folder 9)
    - Texarkana Meeting with Wayne Smith, 1978 October 20-1979 February 9 (Box 270, Folder 10)
    - Natural Gas Policy Act, 1978 September 21-October 25 (Box 270, Folder 11)
    - Mt. Vernon Rotary Club, 1978 August 8-September 28 (Box 270, Folder 12)
    - Texarkana Special Education Center, 1978 September 1-1979 March 28 (Box 270, Folder 13)
    - Texarkana Lions Club, 1978 July 31-October 28 (Box 270, Folder 14)
    - Texarkana Chamber of Commerce, 1978 September 15-November 3 (Box 270, Folder 15)
    - Harrison County Scottish Rite Membership Committee, 1978 September 26-November 3 (Box 270, Folder 16)
    - American Business Women, 1978 September 22-November 15 (Box 270, Folder 17)
    - Linden Lions Club, 1978 August 15-November 3 (Box 270, Folder 18)
    - Atlanta High School, 1978 October 18-November 3 (Box 270, Folder 19)
    - Northeast Texas Education Club, Sulphur Springs, 1978 August 30-November 3 (Box 270, Folder 20)
    - Marshall City Commission, 1977 January 18-1978 November 15 (Box 270, Folder 21)
    - Texarkana Rotary Club, 1978 June 9-November 15 (Box 270, Folder 22)
    - Texarkana Office, 1978 October 6-19 (Box 270, Folder 23)
    - Henderson Chapter, American Association of Retired Persons, Inc., 1978 April 11-November 15 (Box 270, Folder 24)
    - Overton Rotary Club, 1978 September 20-November 15 (Box 270, Folder 25)
    - B. Grueger, J. Hill Texas Democratic party, 1978 September 29-October 26 (Box 270, Folder 26)
    - Marshall Pilot Club, 1978 November 21-December 4 (Box 270, Folder 27)
    - Northeast Texas Municipal Water District, 1978 June 28-November 15 (Box 270, Folder 28)
    - Longhorn Army Ammunition Plant, 1978 July 26-November 15 (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Mt. Pleasant, 1978 October 10-November 15 (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - Athens American Association of Retired Persons, 1978 June 23-November 15 (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Paris, 1978 May 15-November 15 (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Mineola Rotary Club, 1978 July 25-November 15 (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - Texarkana Kiwanis Club, 1978 August 18-November 15 (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - International Paper Company, 1978 October 14-November 15 (Box 271, Folder 7)
    - Clarksville, 1978 August 29-December 4 (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - Jacksonville, 1978 August 14-November 15 (Box 271, Folder 9)
    - Cullen Baker County Fair, 1978 October 18-November 15 (Box 271, Folder 10)
    - Tour of Red River and Lone Star, 1978 September 25-November 16 (Box 271, Folder 11)
    - Dr. Henry Carney Luncheon, 1978 November 8-16 (Box 271, Folder 12)
    - Naples, Reception, 1978 October 28-November 15 (Box 271, Folder 13)
    - Hugh McGuire Moral Issue on TV, 1977 July 8-1978 September 26 (Box 271, Folder 14)
    - Father’s 90th Birthday, Judge Sam B. Hall. Sr., 1978 August 21-September 11 (Box 271, Folder 15)
    - Reception Given by Louise Walters and Inez Shute, New Boston, TX, 1978 October 21 (Box 271, Folder 16)
    - Reception Given by Don and Marguerite Ratcliff, 1978 April 15 (Box 271, Folder 17)
    - Sam B. Hall Reception, Center, TX., 1978 October 17 (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - Texarkana, 1978 January 3-1979 January 15 (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - Sulphur Springs High School, 1978 November 20-1979 January 5 (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - New Boston Chamber of Commerce Banquet, 1978 November 2-1979 January 15 (Box 272, Folder 4)
    - Buster Cole, SW Pump Company, 1979 February 1-20 (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - Paris District Office, 1979 January 10-March 7 (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - January, Other Events, 1978 November 17-1979 January 30 (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - Men’s Breakfast Club, 1979 February 13 (Box 272, Folder 8)
    - Red River Valley Association, 1978 December 21-1979 February 20 (Box 272, Folder 9)
    - Joe D. Waggoner, Jr., Dedication, 1979 January 15-March 29 (Box 272, Folder 10)
    - Perry Huntoon, Texas Association of Railroad Passengers, 1979 February 9-23 (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - Delta County Farm Bureau, 1978 December 15-1979 February 23 (Box 272, Folder 12)
    - East Texas Sales Award Banquet, 1979 January 2-February 23 (Box 272, Folder 13)
    - February, Other Events, 1979 January 12-February 24 (Box 272, Folder 14)
    - Baylor Homecoming, 1979 January 2-February 26 (Box 272, Folder 15)
    - Winnsboro Bank and Trust Company, Dedication, 1978 December 19-1979 March 8 (Box 272, Folder 16)
    - Judicial Conference, Williamsburg (1 of 2), 1979 February 11-May 10 (Box 272, Folder 17)
    - Judicial Conference, Williamsburg (2 of 2), 1978 January 27-1979 March 16 (Box 272, Folder 18)
    - Dangerfield Chamber of Commerce Banquet, 1979 February 24-May 8 (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - Atlanta High School Students, 1979 January 15-April 23 (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Red River Army Depot Change of Command, 1979 March 15 (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Terre Haute Indiana Plyer, Inc., 1979 March 10-April 13 (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - District 5 Farm Bureau Meeting, 1979 February 23-April 27 (Box 273, Folder 5)
    - Marshall District Office, 1979 March 26-April 27 (Box 273, Folder 6)
    - Panola-Harrison Electric Cooperative Inc. Annual Membership Meeting, 1978 December 19-1979 April 27 (Box 273, Folder 7)
    - Paris Office, 1979 April 9-June 15 (Box 273, Folder 8)
    - Red River Valley Deaf and Hearing Association, 1979 January 17-May 1 (Box 273, Folder 9)
    - Robert Cargill, Texas Independent Producers and Royalty Owners Association, 1979 April 5-27 (Box 273, Folder 10)
    - ICI American Inc., 1979 January 16-July 24 (Box 273, Folder 11)
    - Texarkana Chamber of Commerce Governmental Affairs Committee, 1979 February 24-May 1 (Box 273, Folder 12)
    - Soft Drink Bottlers Luncheon, 1979 April 5-26 (Box 273, Folder 13)
    - Atlanta Chamber of Commerce Banquet, 1978 August 4-1979 April 30 (Box 273, Folder 14)
    - Women in Construction Chapter of Texarkana Bosses Night Banquet, 1978 October 25-1979 April 27 (Box 273, Folder 15)
    - East Texas Baptist College Commencement, 1979 March 7-May 8 (Box 273, Folder 16)
    - Caddo Savings and Loan Association, Dedication, 1979 April 8-May 7 (Box 273, Folder 17)
    - District Employee Trip to Washington, 1979 March 16-May 15 (Box 273, Folder 18)
    - Judge Ed Miller Dinner, Texarkana, 1979 May 10 (Box 273, Folder 19)
    - Letter Carriers Union Dinner, 1978 December 21-1979 May 15 (Box 273, Folder 20)
    - Quentin Abernathy Dinner, 1979 April 6-23 (Box 273, Folder 21)
    - Jefferson Junior High Awards Day, 1979 April 5-June 4 (Box 273, Folder 22)
    - Marshall Stagecoach Days, 1978 December 13-1979 June 4 (Box 273, Folder 23)
    - Texas State Society Meeting, 1979 March 29-November 2 (Box 273, Folder 24)
    - Marshall High School Graduating Class, 1978 October 30-1979 June 1 (Box 273, Folder 25)
    - Jack Dillard Waskom Rodeo, 1979 July 11 (Box 273, Folder 26)
    - Henderson, Rusk County Depot, Dedication, 1979 May 18-July 12 (Box 273, Folder 27)
    - First Baptist Church of Marshall, 1979 February 18-July 12 (Box 273, Folder 28)
    - Marshall Rotary Club, 1979 January 23-July 12 (Box 273, Folder 29)
    - Texarkana Crime Project, Morris and W. Smith, 1979 February 14-July 12 (Box 273, Folder 30)
    - Sulphur Springs, Perry Bradley, 1979 July 6-17 (Box 273, Folder 31)
    - God and Country Day, Carthage, Jim Holder, 1979 May 23-August 22 (Box 273, Folder 32)
    - Beeman Jones Retirement Party, 1979 April 25-August 22 (Box 273, Folder 33)
    - Franklin County Library, 1979 July 6-August 29 (Box 273, Folder 34)
    - Texas Association of Hospitals Governing Boards, Ft. Worth, 1979 July 16-October 1 (Box 273, Folder 35)
    - Meeting in Henderson, 1979 July 23-September 15 (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - Longview Chamber of Commerce, 1979 July 24-August 27 (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - Linden Lions Club, 1979 July 24-September 6 (Box 274, Folder 3)
    - Meeting with Realtors in Marshall office, 1979 July 24-August 24 (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - Marshall Jaycees, 1979 July 24-September 6 (Box 274, Folder 5)
    - Texarkana District Office, 1979 July 9-September 5 (Box 274, Folder 6)
    - East Texas Treatment Center, 1979 July 27-September 5 (Box 274, Folder 7)
    - Trip to Rusk, 1979 July 31-September 18 (Box 274, Folder 8)
    - Carthage Noon Lions Club, 1979 July 24-September 5 (Box 274, Folder 9)
    - Overton Rotary Club, 1979 July 31-September 10 (Box 274, Folder 10)
    - National Soft Drink Association Dinner, 1979 September 18-October 5 (Box 274, Folder 11)
    - W.R. Poage Legislative Library, Dedication and Luncheon, 1979 August 13-September 26 (Box 274, Folder 12)
    - Hallsville Western Days, 1979 August 23-27 (Box 274, Folder 13)
    - Henderson High School, Dedication, 1977 April 29-1979 October 5 (Box 274, Folder 14)
    - Northeast Texas Health Systems Agency, Inc., 1979 August 17-October 12 (Box 274, Folder 15)
    - Meeting with Corps of Engineers in Sulphur Springs, 1979 August 20-October 10 (Box 274, Folder 16)
    - Meeting with County Judge and Commissioners, 1979 June 27-October 22 (Box 274, Folder 17)
    - Cattlemen of Cass County, 1979 October 2-11 (Box 274, Folder 18)
    - Trinity Episcopal Day School, 1979 October 4-25 (Box 274, Folder 19)
    - Texas State Society, Board of Directors Meeting, 1979 August 16-November 2 (Box 274, Folder 20)
    - Jim Wright Dinner, 1979 August 18-October 13 (Box 274, Folder 21)
    - Baylor versus Army, 1979 October 20 (Box 274, Folder 22)
    - Domestic Women of Fannin County, 1979 February 3-October 22 (Box 274, Folder 23)
    - Gilmer Jamboree, 1979 September 5-October 27 (Box 274, Folder 24)
    - East Texas Chapter of Credit Unions, 1979 March 23-October 11 (Box 274, Folder 25)
    - Martin Frost Fundraising Dinner, 1979 July 31-August 1 (Box 274, Folder 26)
    - Texarkana Black Chamber of Commerce, Hopkins Airport Dedication, 1979 April 30 (Box 274, Folder 27)
    - Marshall Chamber of Commerce, recognition Dinner, 1979 July 10-October 12 (Box 274, Folder 28)
    - An Evening with Carter and Mondale, 1979 October 22-November 15 (Box 274, Folder 29)
    - Travis Christian College, 1979 April 20-October 30 (Box 274, Folder 30)
    - Texas State Society Meeting, Board of Directors, 1977 November 30-1979 December 6 (Box 274, Folder 31)
    - East Texas Chapter of Bank Administration, Kilgore, 1979 July 5-November 5 (Box 274, Folder 32)
    - Receptions, January, 1979 November 24-1980 February 18 (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Ruff, Howard J. The Ruff Times, 1980 January 1 (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Sam Rayburn’s 98th birthday, 1979 November 12-1980 February 19 (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Meeting in Paris, 1979 September 10-1980 February 4 (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Texas Chapter Gulf States Section, Society of American Foresters, 1979 December 5-18 (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Mt. Pleasant Lions Club, 1980 January 11-18 (Box 275, Folder 6)
    - Overton Public Housing Authority Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1976 June 30-1980 December 28 (Box 275, Folder 7)
    - Norman Carlson, et al, FCI tour in Texarkana, 1979 November 8-1980 January 28 (Box 275, Folder 8)
    - Meet with FAA Officials and Local City Officials, 1979 July 10-1980 February 20 (Box 275, Folder 9)
    - Clarksville Meeting with Farmers, 1979 December 28-1980 February 4 (Box 275, Folder 10)
    - Judicial Conference in Williamsburg (1 of 2), 1979 August 7-1980 May 5 (Box 275, Folder 11)
    - Judicial Conference in Williamsburg (2 of 2), 1979 October 24-1980 January 20 (Box 275, Folder 12)
    - Dedication of Texarkana Public Library, 1977 August 19-1980 February 19 (Box 275, Folder 13)
    - Texas Democratic Delegation, 1979 February 5-1980 March 29 (Box 275, Folder 14)
    - Texas Bottlers Association, 1980 November 21-1981 March 19 (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Red River Valley Association, 1979 December 12-1980 February 26 (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - Carthage Chamber of Commerce Banquet, 1976 December 17-1980 February 22 (Box 276, Folder 3)
    - Marion County Chamber of Commerce Banquet, 1979 November 19-1980 March 11 (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - Marshall Career Days Program, 1979 October 10-1980 January 21 (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - Reception in Texarkana Hosted by Judge Ed Miller, 1980 February 7-27 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - Dedication of San Augustine City Hall, 1980 January 30-May 5 (Box 276, Folder 7)
    - Trip to Georgia with Bo Ginn, 1980 February 27-March 26 (Box 276, Folder 8)
    - Atlanta High School Students, 1979 December 3-1980 May 28 (Box 276, Folder 9)
    - Henderson County Junior College, 1980 January 21-March 31 (Box 276, Folder 10)